[Music]
foreign
we've been wondering a lot about the
various nicknames that people have given
you or you've given yourself so we're
just kind of curious about the back
story of some of the nicknames okay that
you are famous for so the first one and
actually one of my favorites is Joe Burr
yeah so the B with all the R's well I
think
that one came when I started wearing my
jewelry
I'm not positive yeah my eyes exactly
I'm not entirely sure but I guess that's
where it came from so that was like one
that you didn't come up with that I
didn't start calling yourself I can't
say I started calling myself anything I
think that I don't think you can give
yourself a nickname okay that's fair uh
what about Joey franchise CJ uzama
started calling me that he was our tight
end last year yeah he number one pick
that's what he started calling yes I
like it Joe cool
I have no idea where that one came from
but I do like that one okay we have also
smoking Joe I've smoked a cigar too in
my day that is true I remember after uh
the college national championship
exactly what about Tiger King see I
don't like that one that much
I don't know where that that one I don't
like that show I don't like I've not
seen the show because I'm I don't like
seeing animals in cages I don't correct
I don't really like that and so I didn't
see the show so I don't like that
nickname what about Joe Chill
I can't say I've heard that one before
and the other really popular one I've
seen is Joe shiesty yeah that was from a
Creator on social media he made a funny
video and started calling me that that
one I like that one okay yeah very good
[Music]